<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<work-item>
    <field id="author">daniel.morris</field>
    <field id="created">2012-05-09 05:40:17.341 -0400</field>
    <field id="description" text-type="text/html">On our second part of test execution we will test offline. You will not always have an internet connection to your Polarion server but you should be able to test offline. Polarion delivers an offline testing solution you should already know. An export to MS Excel which exports our test cases and a reimport of our test results. &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goto our test run &amp;quot;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt;line-height: 1.5;"&gt;i1_SmokeTest_Team A&lt;/span&gt;&amp;quot; and click on &amp;quot;Export Tests to Excel&amp;quot; below the &amp;quot;Execute Test&amp;quot; Button we use before.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now you will get an Excel file with all remaning test cases. You should recognize this sort of Excel file. It is similar to our Excel Round-Trip file. You can only change test results and add some comments to these test cases. Repeat the working steps you did before in Polarion. Set one test case to passed and one to failed. Don´t forget to write a comment why one of the test cases failed. We need this comment for our next step.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;img style="width: 724px;height: 196px;" src="workitemimg:1-exportExcel.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;After testing offline we can reimport our file to Polarion by clicking &amp;quot;Import Results from Excel&amp;quot; below the export button.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review how our test run report has changed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;table style="width: 80%;margin-left: auto;margin-right: auto;border: 1px solid #CCCCCC;empty-cells: show;border-collapse: collapse;" class="polarion-Document-table" id="polarion_wiki macro name=table"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th style="font-weight: bold;background-color: #F0F0F0;text-align: left;vertical-align: top;height: 12px;border: 1px solid #CCCCCC;padding: 5px;"&gt;Hint: Similar to online execution of test cases, electronic signatures are also activated for offline execution. So during import of your test results you wil be asked to add your credentials.&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</field>
    <field id="previousStatus">open</field>
    <field id="priority">25.0</field>
    <field id="severity">normal</field>
    <field id="status">open</field>
    <field id="title">Executing test cases using excel</field>
    <field id="type">exercise</field>
</work-item>
